Finding Aid for College of Literature, Science and the Arts (University of Michigan) publications 1871-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sub-Unit Publications
  - Pilot Program
    - Manuals
      - Pilot to Co-Pilots, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Undergraduate Research Opportunity Program
    - Brochures undated (Box 11)
    - Directories
      - Program Directory, 1992-93 (Box 11)
  - Undergraduate Research Program
    - Directories
      - Work Study Participants: A Special Opportunity for Freshmen and Sophomore Minority Students, 1989 (Box 11)
- Student Publications
  The Student Publications series (.2 linear feet) contains publications published by student groups within the College of Literature, Science and the Arts and document the activities and concerns of students during their time at the University of Michigan.
  The Student Publications series includes brochures, journals, manuals, newsletters, and reports published by and about the LSA Student Government. The journal Player was published in the 1997-1998 academic year. It is an anthology of writings by students from the college. There are two manuals, Disorientation released from 1973 to 1976, and the undated Michigopoly published to help familiarize new students to Ann Arbor, the University of Michigan, and the College of Literature, Science and the Arts. In the 1980s there were three newsletters published by LSA Student Government to inform LSA students of the activities of student government in the college. These included the LSA News issued in 1984, the LSA-SG News printed in 1985 and the LSA Journal published in 1985 and 1988. There are also two reports describing the activities of LSA Student Government in 1997 and 1999 including vision and mission statements, student officers and representatives, committee activity reports, survey results, and copies of Michigan Daily articles about LSA Student Government.
  - LSA Student Government
    - Brochures
      - General 1983, undated (Box 11)
      - Grievance Procedures, undated (Box 11)
    - Journals
      - Player, 1997-1998 (Box 11)
    - Manuals
      - Disorientation, 1973-1976, undated (Box 11)
      - Michigopoly, undated (Box 11)
    - Newsletters
      - LSA Journal, 1985, 1988 (Box 11)
      - LSA News, 1984 (Box 11)
      - LSA-SG News, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Posters (Box 11)
    - Reports
      - LS&A Student Government 1998-1999 Report, 1999 (Box 11)
      - A Report on LS&A Student Government, 1997 (Box 11)
- Archived College of LS&A Website
  TheCollege of LS&A Archived Website series documents the academic programs, accomplishments, resources, events, and people at the College of Literature, Science, and the Arts. Content includes important news and announcements, publications (such as newsletters and course catalogs), and information about admissions, curriculum, degree requirements, faculty, and the overall mission of the College. The website series is arranged chronologically, with captures from 2002 and 2003 stored on CD. Starting in 2010, this archived website will be captured on a regular, ongoing basis as part of the University of Michigan Web Archives, hosted at http://webarchives.cdlib.org/a/universityofmichigan/.
  - Website capture May 15, 2002, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 2)
    (Original URL http://www.lsa.umich.edu)
  - Website capture June 23, 2003, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 2)
  - Archived College of Literature, Science, and the Arts home page 2010-[ongoing]
  - Archived websites related to the College of Literature, Science, and the Arts 2010-[ongoing]